Eric C. Paulz

https://epaulz.github.io epaulz@vt.edu | 864-243-6767 Blacksburg, VA

OBJECTIVE

My goal is to use the skills I have gained thus far in my career to contribute to the advancement of science and technology through research and application. I strive to continue learning every day in my professional role and I intend to further my education through graduate school.

EMPLOYMENT

Ted & Karyn Hume Center for National Security & Technology	Blacksburg, VA
Computer Engineer	1/2019 – present
BMW Group – innovation[LAB]	Greenville, SC
IT Innovations & Research Intern	5/2018 - 8/2018
BMW Manufacturing	Greer, SC
Material Control Intern	5/2017 – 8/2017
Clemson Online	Clemson, SC
Educational Media & Web Support Intern	1/2017 – 4/2017
EDUCATION	
Clemson University – Computer Science, B.S. (2018)	Clemson, SC

SKILLS

Software Engineering – Python, C/C++, VBA, Java, Git

Data Science – Python (pandas, numpy, jupyter), SQL, Alation, Tableau

Simulation Modeling – VISSIM, NetLogo, MATLAB

Embedded Software Development – OpenCPI, Xilinx SoC, Embedded Linux

Miscellaneous – Node-RED, Splunk, HTML, Unity 3D, 3D printing

INTERESTS

IoT, cybersecurity, software defined radio, secure wireless communications, machine learning, autonomous vehicles, aviation, WAIC